The eldest has a character that understands the greater good
У старшего сына добродетельный характер
Considers the overall situation
он думает о целом
I believe he will prioritize Xuan Kingdom's future
думаю он поставит будущее страны выше личного
Now Zu Yue controls the army
Сейчас Цзуюэ командует армией
This can also curb Xu'er's impulsive nature
это сможет сдерживать порывистый характер Сюя
With her here
Пока она рядом
Xu'er likely won't easily move against the eldest
Сюй вряд ли посмеет причинить вред брату
Chu Meng
Чу Мэн
Call the second son
Чу Мэн позови младшего
Father
Отец
Father clearly said this wound was almost healed
Отец ведь говорил что рана уже почти зажила
How is this, this
Как же так это
Your elder brother is benevolent and filial
Твой старший брат благочестив
Since you have the edict
у тебя есть указ
He knows it's my intention
он знает что это моя воля
He will never make things difficult for you
и не станет тебе мешать
You understand military affairs
Ты отлично разбираешься в военном деле
These years of warfare
эти годы войн
Have given you sufficient prestige in the army
принесли тебе огромный авторитет в армии
After you succeed
Когда ты унаследуешь трон
Your mother
твоя мать
Will make all the noble families submit to you
сама заставит все знатные семьи повиноваться тебе
As your support
они станут твоей опорой
I believe
Папа верит
Xuan Kingdom's future affairs
что дела Сюаньго в будущем
You can handle well
ты сможешь хорошо вести
But one thing
Но есть одна вещь
I must warn you
папа обязан тебе напомнить
Remember
Запомни
You are family
вы одна семья
Your son
Ваш сын
Will definitely not become estranged from elder brother
никогда не стану враждовать с братом
Those things that make people point fingers
Те дела за которые людей упрекают
In your generation
в вашем поколении
Don't do them anymore
пусть прекратятся
Your son
Ваш сын
Will remember
запомнит
Rise
Встань